# **BS SHRAVAN**

**UI** Designer

heyshrav.com heyshrav@gmail.com

+91 9740269570

#### **INTRODUCTION**

I am a Computer Science Engineer, graduted from the Global Academy of Technology, Bengaluru.

As an Engineering student and a self-taught Designer, I like to bring my technical knowledge and design skills together to try and create meaningful designs and user experience.

Apart from having the experience of interning at 4 different startups and working on various freelance projects, I am also very passionate about photography and visual arts.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Codemonk

Associate UI/UX Engineer

Took the ownership of redesigning Codemonk Website and worked on design implementation of an app, RealIQ - a real estate platform.

Sept 2021 - Nov 2021

#### LocTruth

UI/UX Intern

Worked on redesigning the main platform, marketing materials and assisted in front-end design implementation.

Mar 2021 - June 2021

#### KlapKlap

UI/UX Intern

Worked on conceptualizing user interface for iOS, improving in-app user experience and gamification process.

June 2020 - July 2020

#### **Crimson Tech**

Graphics Design Intern

Worked on creating marketing material, improving website UI, social media marketing designs and handling social media accounts.

May 2020 - Sept 2020

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Global Academy of Technology**

Bachelor's of Engineering, Computer Science

2017 - 2021 I Bengaluru, India

## Maharishi Vidya Mandir Sr. Secondary School

CBSE, PCM + Information Practices

2015 - 2017 | Noida, India

### **SKILLS**

### Design Skills

# Soft Skills

Wireframing Team Leadership
Rapid Prototyping Project Management
Problem Solving Team Management
Design Thinking & Research Public Speaking

# **Design Tools**

# Technical Skills

Figma HTML

Adobe XD CSS

Adobe Illustrator Bootstrap

Adobe Photoshop ReactJS

Wireframe Sketching MySQL

Framer WordPress

### **OTHER WORK**

## Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador Program

Alpha Student Ambassador

Learn Student Ambassadors are a global group of campus leaders who are eager to help fellow students, create robust tech communities and develop technical and career skills for the future.

Aug 2020 - Present

## Upwork

Freelance Designer

Working as a Freelance Graphics & Web Designer on various projects in my free time for clients on Upwork.

Nov 2020 - Present